https://ohiostatebuckeyes.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Site is designed to be in compliance with the DAA Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising and the NAI Code of Conduct and the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Europe Framework for OBA.  Click here if you would like further information regarding the DAA Self-Regulatory Principles or here if you would like more information regarding the NAI Code of Conduct or here if you would like further information about the IAB Europe’s OBA Framework.
IF LOCATED IN THE EUROPEAN UNION (EU), REFERENCES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY TO WHAT WE DO WITH PERSONAL DATA ARE MORE FULLY EXPLAINED IN RIGHTS FOR EU USERS BELOW.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
We collect information from you when you visit the Sites including information regarding your browsing, usage, and interactions.  We also collect information that allows us to identify browsers and devices we have interacted with previously. The information that we collect about you: the type of Internet browser, browser language and operating system you use; your device’s Internet protocol (“IP”) address; access dates and times; unique device identifiers as well as hardware or operating system device identifiers (e.g., IDFA for iOS and AAID for Android); connection type (wired or Wi-Fi); the region where your device is located; network to which your device is connected; longitude/latitude of a (mobile) device; SDK data; engagement data; geo-IP data; the mobile carrier (if available); the website you came from before, and visited after; and information related to the pages you are viewing on the Website.
We also collect personal information, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address from the Site only when you choose to provide it to us in a form or by registering as a publisher.  You may also submit personal information such as name and email address to subscribe to one of our newsletters.
COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
“Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a website for facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that website. We and certain third-party business partners, vendors and advertisers may use cookies (or clear gifs, web beacons or similar devices, including devices that function in the mobile environment) to collect information and other behavioral data from you for purposes such as targeting advertising services and better understanding the effectiveness of our advertisements. To learn about cookies in general you may visit www.iab-performance-marketing-explained.net or http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
We use different types of cookies and some cookies are put into the following categories (please note that some cookies may be used differently by different Business Customers):
Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognize a return visitor to the website.
Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to the website. This enables us to personalize advertising content for you, and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to the website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We use this information to make the advertising displayed to you more relevant to your interests.
WEB BROWSER/COOKIE-BASED OPT-OUTS
You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. There are also many programs that allow you to manually delete your cookies.
The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads/interest-based advertising from us, our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You may use the NAI opt-out tool at https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/, which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and other members. The DAA’s opt-out tool can be found at https://www.aboutads.info/choices/.  EU users who have provided their consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies to process their personal information can use the EDAA’s opt-out tool which can be found at https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/.
To be clear, the opt-out from targeted ads must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted out. For example, if you have opted out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device.  However, once you have opted out on one device (“Opted-Out Device”), we will not use any new data from the Opted-Out Device to identify you on another device for interest-based advertising purposes, and will not use data from another device for interest-based advertising purposes on the Opted-Out Device.
If you erase or otherwise alter your cookie/device settings (including upgrading certain browsers or devices) you may need to perform each opt-out process again, unless we can match the device as outlined above.
Even if you opt out of targeted ads based on cookies, you may still see ads based on other general factors such as webpage context or browser type.
